Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. John F. Devine Papers, 1952-1974 and undated, bulk 1956-1970 RL.00683
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Oversize Materials
  - Radio/Television Department Series, 1955-1962 and undated
    - Client Subseries, 1955-1962 and undated
      - 1958
        - Ford Motor Company
          - Tennessee Ernie Ford episode advertisements (Oversize-folder 2)
            - Oct. 2 including smaller sections depicting other Ford Motor Company shows (Oversize-folder 2)
            - Oct. 9 including smaller sections depicting other Ford Motor Company shows (Oversize-folder 2)
            - Oct. 9 including program with Ann Blythe (Oversize-folder 2)
            - Oct. 16 including program with Ernie Kovacs (Oversize-folder 2)
            - Oct. 23 including program with William (Bill) Bendix (Oversize-folder 2)
            - Nov. 6 including program with Jane Wyman advertisement (Oversize-folder 2)
            - Nov. 13 including program with Charlie Weaver (Cliff Arquette) (Oversize-folder 2)
            - "NBC's Audience Building Plans," undated (Oversize-folder 2)
          - Suspicion show advertisements
            - Heartbeat, Feb. 3 (Oversize-folder 2)
            - Four O'Clock, produced by Alfred Hitchcock, Sept. 30 (Oversize-folder 2)
          - Wagon Train show advertisements
            - Around the Horn, Oct. 1, two advertisements (Oversize-folder 2)
            - The Jennifer Churchill Story, Oct. 15 (Oversize-folder 2)
            - The Tobias Jones Story, Oct. 22 (Oversize-folder 2)
      - 1962
        - Ford Motor Company
          - Sweepstakes advertisement (1962 Ford Galaxie 500 convertible), undated (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Programming Subseries, 1956
      - New York office
        - House advertising for "Live Local TV Group," Aug. and Sept. 1956 (Oversize-folder 2)
    - Research Subseries, 1955
      - Consumer Panel
        - House advertising featuring the JWT Consumer Panel (Oversize-folder 2)
          - March 1955 (Oversize-folder 2)
          - January and March 1955 (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Corporate Administration Series, 1962-1968 and undated
    - Committees/Groups Subseries, 1963 and undated
      - Meeting Club
        - Architectural rendering of employee cocktail club bar at 420 Lexington, New York, New York, undated (Oversize-folder 3)
      - New York Operations Committee
        - Ad for New York Telephone, 1963 June 26 (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Office Files Subseries, 1962-1968 and undated
      - 1962
        - Norman H. Strouse
          - Advertisements promoting purchase of U. S. Savings bonds, undated, three advertisements (Oversize-folder 3)
      - 1964
        - JWT 100th anniversary
          - Sunset magazine ad in Advertising Age, Special Section, J. Walter Thompson Centennial Issue, 1964 Dec. 7 (Oversize-folder 3)
      - 1968
        - Minority relations
          - RCA color television magazine advertisement featuring actor Bill Cosby in Ebony magazine, 1968 Mar. (Oversize-folder 3)
    - Offices Subseries, 1968
      - Canada
        - Proposed layout sketch for JWT office in Place Bonaventure in Montreal, Canada, 1968 Aug. 1 (Oversize-folder 3)
        - Architectural drawings depicting revisions to office at 23 Ranchmore Road, Ontario, 1968 Apr. 2 (Oversize-folder 3)